to help me with today's exam please
welcome our new nightly show Optics
expert real life eye surgeon and
Kentucky Senator Ram
Paul hey R welcome to the show R happy
seat there you
go thanks thanks for taking the time to
be on uh uh our being our nightly show
Optics expert okay so I mean I assumed
you'd be too busy with the presidential
debates and I'm going to be like a
correspond it right uh Larry you're
breaking up a little bit you right here
I'm right oh I'm right here being okay
exactly uh okay so so now as an eye
surgeon
uh uh what's your take on Donald Trump
well you know
Larry have you ever had a speck of dirt
fly into your eye yeah I mean that's
really annoying yeah yeah annoying
irritating mighty even make you
cry sure sure I'm with you but if the
dirt doesn't go away it'll keep
scratching away at your cornea until
eventually blind you with all its filth
and then it makes fun of you on
CNN think you got a little personal in
there uh I got it so you're saying that
I is a conservative voter and Donald
Trump is the speck of dirt right no
Larry Donald Trump is a delusional
narcissist and an orange faed
windbag
okay a speck of dirt is way more
qualified to be
brother well said our new correspondent
Ram Paul everybody thank you thank you
you're breaking up a bit no you don't
have to do that oh I'm sorry well thanks
for having fun with us do you have time
to answer a couple of questions actually
that that was very you have fun doing
questions very easy question uh this is
very easy why are you running in the
Republican party I don't understand that
I mean you're Pro weed uh you're like no
no no I'm just not anti- no you're proed
I'm just not anti-weed okay whatever you
said you you help people with their
glaucoma you're Pro we right okay anti-
prison industrial complex you've talked
uh very eloquently about prison reform
is there like a middle ground of people
that you're looking for that aren't
Republican aren't Democrat are there
people in there like huge there there
are people from both sides that we're
trying to get from the right there are
people who believe in economic Liberty
from the left there are people who
believe in personal Liberty and really
what we're trying to do is join Liberty
together to say you know what across the
board government ought to stay out of
your life Jeb Bush said he'd go back in
time and kill Baby Hitler okay um would
you go back in time and stop baby Trump
from being
born you know I'm not sure I would say
that Trump is Hitler go go I'm not
saying that Gobles maybe but I'm not
saying Hitler I'm not going really so
you're really you're going there then no
no no I've said he wasn't no I I I
steadfastly said he was not Hitler but
maybe goal but I have seriously compared
him to Gollum from The Lord of the Rings
yes I understand where go was WR you
know my precious you know the Ring The
Ring of Power that's very scary what you
just did yeah I know I
know but what I'm what I've been trying
to tell people is what worries me most
about Trump other than all the other
crazy things is that I believe that he
wants power and I believe from my point
of view that power corrupts and that the
whole purpose of our founding fathers in
our country was to contain power the
Constitution was to restrain the size of
government and keep power at a minimum
and I don't want power to gravitate to a
Republican or a Democrat yeah go
ahead you are certainly your own
candidate you don't you don't seem to
follow any side you follow your own path
and I think that's really something all
right are you ready to play uh keep it
100 to answer keep it 100 question he
that okay was I really good at this game
yes no you have to do this you have to
keep your answer 100% real ready okay
other than Donald Trump can't mention
Trump okay who is the biggest dick of
all the GOP candidates right now and I
know you have an
answer Larry I think you're breaking up
your um can you uh help us uh who is it
come on who is it you know just say Ted
Cruz he's the biggest tool right just
say Ted Cruz is a tool Larry just say
that see before we came on here just say
Ted Cruz is a tool please just say it
just say it D just say it came on here
say it just say take Cruz the tool R
Paul everybody that's all we
[Applause]
got